Now what we want to do is if the user has already logged their information for the day,
现在 假设用户已经记录了当天的信息
what we want to do is make sure that we show this screen where we say,
我们要做的是确保显示这个屏幕消息
"You've already logged your information."
"You already logged your information for today.”
And we give them the option to reset their information.
并使用户能够重置信息
This is iOS and this is Android over here on the right.
左边是 iOS 版本 右边是 Android 版本
So the very first thing we'll do is inside of add entry,
首先 在 AddEntry 中
let's go ahead and import a few things.
导入一些内容
First, let's make sure we
先确保导入 Ionicons
import Ionicons because that's the icon component we'll be using.
因为我们将使用该图标组件
And then, what we will do is down here inside of our render method is,
然后在下面的 render 方法中
let's just say if.this.props.alreadyLogged and we will eventually pass in this as a prop.
输入 if (this.props.alreadyLogged) 我们最终将导入这个属性
But we will set it up right now just so that when we do, it's all ready for us.
但是现在将设置下 以便在使用时能够直接拿来用
So, if we've already logged our information,
如果已经记录了信息
then what we want to return is a view inside of this view.
则返回一个 View
Let's go ahead and render our Ionicons icon.
在该 View 中渲染 Ionicons 图标
Let's say, ios-happy-outline and then the size we will say 100.
名称设为 ios-happy-outline 大小设为 100
And then under this we will have a text that says,
然后在下面输出文本
"You already logged your information for today."
"You already logged your information for today."
And then what we want to do is we want to have right here a reset button.
然后在这里添加一个重置按钮
So that way we can hit this button and it'll reset.
这样我们就能点击该按钮并重置信息
This is going to be a pretty common component.
这将是一个非常常见的组件
You'll notice that this button is right here,
你将在这里看到这个按钮
it's just a text button.
它是一个文本按钮
So what we'll do is we will actually create this because we're
现在我们将创建该按钮
going to use this text button a few other places in our app.
因为我们在应用的其他几个地方也会用到该按钮
So let's just call it textbutton.js.
称其为 TextButton.js
It's going to be a button,
它将是一个按钮
so we'll need a few things,
因此需要导入一些内容
text as well as we'll use TouchableOpacity both coming from React Native.
导入 Text 和 TouchableOpacity 二者都来自 react-native
It is going to be a stateless functional component
它将是一个无状态函数式组件
and it is going to receive a few different things.
并且将接收几项不同的参数
Children. And then onPress.
包括 Children 和 onPress
We want to return TouchableOpacity onPress,
返回 TouchableOpacity 和 onPress
we're obviously going to call onPress that we're passing in.
很明显要调用传入的 onPress
And then what we'll do here is we will just render.
然后渲染 children
"Children", wrapping it in a text component.
将其封装在 Text 组件中
So, now, inside of add entry,
转到 AddEntry
let's go ahead and import that and then now what we want to do is down here,
导入 TextButton
right here, let's go ahead and render our text button.
然后向下滚动到这里并渲染 TextButton
Inside of it, let's just go ahead and say reset and then now what we need to do,
在里面输入 Reset
we need to pass it a method to run whenever it's clicked.
现在需要传入一个按钮被点击时运行的方法
So what we can do is let's go ahead and add a reset method here.
我们在这里添加 Reset 方法
We will grab the key for today,
获取今天的 key
which again we can get by calling timeToString.
可以通过调用 timeToString 来获取
And then again, what we're going to do,
然后就像在这里的
just like we're doing up here in submit,
submit 方法中一样
eventually, we'll do a few other things.
最终我们将执行几项操作
Let's just make a note to ourselves,
先添加几条注释
so we want to update Redux.
我们将更新 Redux
We then want to route to home and we then want to update our database.
然后转到主屏幕 并更新数据库
So all of those we will do in a future lesson.
我们将在后面的课程中完成所有这些操作
But now we have reset that we can then pass to our text button component.
现在已经创建好 Reset 可以将其传入 TextButton 组件中
So now this looks good,
看起来正常
just to test this is working,
测试下是否可行
instead of saying, if this.props.alreadyLogged let's just change this to true.
将 this.props.alreadyLogged 改成 true
Looks like we have a syntax error on line 90,
看来第 90 行存在语法错误
that should be equals.
应该是等号
And it looks like we are getting another issue where we probably have
似乎还有一个问题 可能有拼写错误
a typo name ios-happy-outline. There we go.
名称应该为“ios-happy-outline” ouline 拼错了
Alright, so we have this view.
出现了这个视图
Now when we hit reset nothing happens,
点击 Reset 什么也没发生
but eventually it will happen.
最终会有后续效果的
So let's just go ahead before we end and change this back to this.props.alreadyLogged.
结束之前 先将这个再改为 this.props.alreadyLogged